(Leonard:)Did you hear about this study
that found people
(Leonard:)that were cool and popular
at 13
(Leonard:)have problems succeeding
later in life?
(Raj:)Hmm. I'm doing okay,
and I was very popular at 13.
(Penny:)In school?
(Raj:)Oh, no. At home.
(Raj:)The servants would sing to me,
(Raj:)laugh at my jokes...
(Raj:)I wish I knew their names.
(Penny:)Does the study say what happens
to the unpopular kids?
(Leonard:)You tell me... you woke up
in bed with one.
(Sheldon:)Listen to this.
(Sheldon:)I just received an e-mail
from Wil Wheaton.
(Sheldon:)Leonard Nimoy's son is
working on a documentary
(Sheldon:)that he started with his
father before he passed away.
(Sheldon:)It's about Mr. Spock and
his impact on our culture.
(Raj:)Hmm.
(Leonard:)Why is he writing to you?
(Sheldon:)Well, they're looking
for fans to interview,
(Sheldon:)and Wil thought
I'd be good for it.
(Raj:)Oh. Hey, high five.
(Sheldon:)Absolutely not.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, Penny,
(Sheldon:)you spent some time
in front
(Sheldon:)of the camera.
Any words of advice?
(Penny:)Yes. Don't take your shirt off
(Penny:)just because the director
said so.
(Sheldon:)This is a documentary
about Mr. Spock.
(Sheldon:)I'm sure if there's nudity,
it will be tasteful.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪